{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571af"},"question":"Who announced that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue the browser plugin in January 2016?","answer":"Oracle","sentence":"In January 2016, Oracle announced that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue the browser plugin.","score":"3.5505296190283597","choices":["Germany","Bahrain","America","Oracle"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b0"},"question":"Who is the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform?","answer":"Oracle Corporation","sentence":"Oracle Corporation is the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform, following their acquisition of Sun Microsystems on January 27,2010.","score":"3.4039559907502164","choices":["Oracle Corporation","James Hockey Red Hat Software","Robert Clinton Apple","Paul Sernoty SAP"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b1"},"question":"Whose trademark license for usage of the Java brand insists that all implementations be compatible?","answer":"Sun's trademark license for usage of the Java brand","sentence":"Historically, Sun's trademark license for usage of the Java brand insists that all implementations be compatible.","score":"3.3827303336472885","choices":["Germany's signature licences for refers of the C++ products","America's infringement licensing for e.g. of the Python marketing","Sun's trademark license for usage of the Java brand","Phoenix's patent licence for use of the C product"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b2"},"question":"When did Oracle announce that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue the browser plugin?","answer":"in January 2016","sentence":"In January 2016, Oracle announced that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue the browser plugin.","score":"3.372736880853154","choices":["in february 2014","in december 2018","in January 2016","in october 2015"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b3"},"question":"What does Java servlet technology provide Web developers with?","answer":"with a simple, consistent mechanism for extending the functionality of a Web server and for accessing existing business systems","sentence":"Java servlet technology provides Web developers with a simple, consistent mechanism for extending the functionality of a Web server and for accessing existing business systems.","score":"3.3564234499461243","choices":["with a straightforward, inconsistent framework for extend the interface of a internet desktop and for access expand businesses system","with a easy, solid system for extended the built-in of a online software and for downloading current industry technologies","with a simple, consistent mechanism for extending the functionality of a Web server and for accessing existing business systems","with a rather, strong facilitate for extends the interfaces of a website browser and for accessed build companies devices"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b4"},"question":"Who did Oracle announce that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue in January 2016?","answer":"the browser plugin","sentence":"In January 2016, Oracle announced that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue the browser plugin.","score":"3.3248504268612904","choices":["the netscape javascript","the firefox add-on","the browser plugin","the microsoft sdk"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b5"},"question":"Who is another notable Java SE implementation that is licensed under the GNU GPL?","answer":"OpenJDK","sentence":"OpenJDK is another notable Java SE implementation that is licensed under the GNU GPL.","score":"3.3230978546525476","choices":["Sillicon Graphics","Red Hat Software","OpenJDK","AMD"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b6"},"question":"Who aims to replace CMS with the Garbage-First Collector?","answer":"Oracle","sentence":"Oracle aims to replace CMS with the Garbage-First Collector.","score":"3.2744090152036844","choices":["Texas","San Antonio","Oracle","Bahrain"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b7"},"question":"Who resigned from Oracle on April 2,2010?","answer":"James Gosling","sentence":"On April 2,2010, James Gosling resigned from Oracle.","score":"3.2733191419537624","choices":["John Thomas callum","James Gosling","James Hockey ryan","George Flank phillippe"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b8"},"question":"What led to a legal dispute between Oracle and Google?","answer":"the use of Java-related technology in Android","sentence":"The use of Java-related technology in Android led to a legal dispute between Oracle and Google.","score":"3.2598332193955404","choices":["the allow of Java-related technological in Richard Mccullam","the use of Java-related technology in Android","the using of Java-related tech in George Flank","the used of Java-related technologies in Charles Page"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571b9"},"question":"When was Java released as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform?","answer":"in 1995","sentence":"Java was originally developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems (which has since been acquired by Oracle) and released in 1995 as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform.","score":"3.2431667633180488","choices":["in 1995","in 1993","in 1996","in 1994"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ba"},"question":"Whose vice-president Rich Green said that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist?","answer":"Sun's vice-president Rich Green","sentence":"Sun's vice-president Rich Green said that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist.","score":"3.2300068274629847","choices":["San Antonio's secretary-treasurer Paul Sernoty","Texas's treasurer Richard Mccullam","Sun's vice-president Rich Green","Michigan's vice-chairman Charles Page"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571bb"},"question":"What was released in 1995 as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform?","answer":"Java","sentence":"Java was originally developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems (which has since been acquired by Oracle) and released in 1995 as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform.","score":"3.229623851474953","choices":["Python","Java","C","C++"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571bc"},"question":"What is the bytecode language supported by the Android SDK incompatible with?","answer":"with Java bytecode","sentence":"The bytecode language supported by the Android SDK is incompatible with Java bytecode and runs on its own virtual machine, optimized for low-memory devices such as smartphones and tablet computers.","score":"3.2110030796141653","choices":["with Java bytecode","with C++ p-code","with Python runtime","with C jvm"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571bd"},"question":"Where is Platform-independent Java essential?","answer":"to Java EE","sentence":"Platform-independent Java is essential to Java EE, and an even more rigorous validation is required to certify an implementation.","score":"3.2082721777500818","choices":["to Python uh","to Java EE","to C lihn","to C++ sah"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571be"},"question":"Who said that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist?","answer":"Sun's vice-president Rich Green","sentence":"Sun's vice-president Rich Green said that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist.","score":"3.2055835081008612","choices":["Germany's secretary-treasurer Richard Mccullam","San Antonio's treasurer Paul Sernoty","Sun's vice-president Rich Green","Bahrain's vice-chairman Johann Carry"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571bf"},"question":"Whose ideal role with regard to Java did Sun's vice-president Rich Green say as?","answer":"that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist","sentence":"Sun's vice-president Rich Green said that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist.","score":"3.199388281546596","choices":["that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist","that moon's perfect character with particular to C++ was as an televangelist","that sunlight's optimal supporting with regarding to Python was as an evangelical","that microsystems's suitable as with respect to C was as an preacher"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c0"},"question":"Who are server-side Java EE components that generate responses?","answer":"JavaServer Pages","sentence":"JavaServer Pages are server-side Java EE components that generate responses, typically HTML pages, to HTTP requests from clients.","score":"3.199241065703169","choices":["JavaServer Pages","servlets page","ecocriticism printed","jsp books"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c1"},"question":"What is Oracle Corporation the current owner of?","answer":"of the official implementation of the Java SE platform","sentence":"Oracle Corporation is the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform, following their acquisition of Sun Microsystems on January 27,2010.","score":"3.1878293560934416","choices":["of the according implement of the Paul Sernoty framework","of the official implementation of the Java SE platform","of the saying implemented of the Richard Mccullam support","of the ministry implementing of the George Flank supports"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c2"},"question":"What started when Sun began releasing the Java source code under the GPL?","answer":"the implementation","sentence":"The implementation started when Sun began releasing the Java source code under the GPL.","score":"3.185851198931593","choices":["the implementation","the implement","the implementing","the implemented"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c3"},"question":"Who does Oracle aim to replace CMS with?","answer":"with the Garbage-First Collector","sentence":"Oracle aims to replace CMS with the Garbage-First Collector.","score":"3.1841333596958896","choices":["with the Garbage-First collectors","with the Garbage-First Collector","with the Garbage-First connoisseur","with the Garbage-First collection"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c4"},"question":"What did Sun generate revenue from Java through?","answer":"through the selling of licenses for specialized products such as the Java Enterprise System","sentence":"Sun generated revenue from Java through the selling of licenses for specialized products such as the Java Enterprise System.","score":"3.184049676442742","choices":["through the buying of license for specialised product such as the Paul Sernoty","through the sold of licence for specialize imported such as the David Hyland","through the sell of licences for specializing goods such as the John Thomas","through the selling of licenses for specialized products such as the Java Enterprise System"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c5"},"question":"Who did Sun's vice-president Rich Green say as?","answer":"that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist","sentence":"Sun's vice-president Rich Green said that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist.","score":"3.177542812584494","choices":["that moon's perfect character with particular to C++ was as an televangelist","that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist","that microsystems's suitable as with respect to C was as an preacher","that sunlight's optimal supporting with regarding to Python was as an evangelical"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c6"},"question":"What did Sun also provide superseded by later, standards-based Java ME configuration-profile pairings?","answer":"an edition called Personal Java that has been","sentence":"Sun also provided an edition called Personal Java that has been superseded by later, standards-based Java ME configuration-profile pairings.","score":"3.171421276337767","choices":["an published known IBM that has been","an edition called Personal Java that has been","an version referred Nvidia that has been","an titled calling Sillicon Graphics that has been"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c7"},"question":"What sent down the case of determining the damages to federal court in San Francisco?","answer":"the Appeals Court","sentence":"On March 2018, this ruling was overturned by the Appeals Court, which sent down the case of determining the damages to federal court in San Francisco.","score":"3.1672126116186226","choices":["the Appeals Court","the upheld appeals","the appeal courts","the court judge"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c8"},"question":"What was initially called Oak after an oak tree that stood outside Gosling's office?","answer":"the language","sentence":"The language was initially called Oak after an oak tree that stood outside Gosling's office.","score":"3.1659588045800278","choices":["the arabic","the language","the word","the english"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571c9"},"question":"Who was the Java 1. 0 compiler re-written in Java by to comply strictly with the Java 1. 0 language specification?","answer":"by Arthur van Hoff","sentence":"The Java 1. 0 compiler was re-written in Java by Arthur van Hoff to comply strictly with the Java 1. 0 language specification.","score":"3.161862462275308","choices":["by David Hyland nistelrooy James Hockey","by Arthur van Hoff","by Richard Mccullam gogh Paul Sernoty","by Robert Clinton der Robert Clinton"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ca"},"question":"When did James Gosling resign from Oracle?","answer":"on April 2,2010","sentence":"On April 2,2010, James Gosling resigned from Oracle.","score":"3.1599638524371056","choices":["on october 2,2010","on july 2,2010","on june 2,2010","on April 2,2010"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571cb"},"question":"Who released the first public implementation as Java 1. 0 in 1996?","answer":"Sun Microsystems","sentence":"Sun Microsystems released the first public implementation as Java 1. 0 in 1996.","score":"3.1599078627141237","choices":["Red Hat Software","Sillicon Graphics","Sun Microsystems","Nvidia"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571cc"},"question":"What does Oracle Corporation follow on January 27,2010?","answer":"i. e.'s acquisition of Sun Microsystems","sentence":"Oracle Corporation is the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform, following their acquisition of Sun Microsystems on January 27,2010.","score":"3.150564445283326","choices":["a. a.'s merger of Sillicon Graphics","l. g.'s acquire of IBM","r. j.'s purchase of Intel","i. e.'s acquisition of Sun Microsystems"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571cd"},"question":"What was originally developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems?","answer":"Java","sentence":"Java was originally developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems (which has since been acquired by Oracle) and released in 1995 as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform.","score":"3.136802644868141","choices":["Java","Python","C++","C"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ce"},"question":"Who did James Gosling resign from on April 2,2010?","answer":"from Oracle","sentence":"On April 2,2010, James Gosling resigned from Oracle.","score":"3.136162690011214","choices":["from America","from San Antonio","from Oracle","from Texas"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571cf"},"question":"What is intended to replace Swing as the standard GUI library for Java SE?","answer":"JavaFX","sentence":"JavaFX is intended to replace Swing as the standard GUI library for Java SE, but both will be included for the foreseeable future.","score":"3.129683560840834","choices":["San Antonio","JavaFX","Bahrain","Boston"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d0"},"question":"Who embed Java code in an HTML page by using the special delimiters?","answer":"jSPs","sentence":"JSPs embed Java code in an HTML page by using the special delimiters (% and %).","score":"3.1288564083976858","choices":["Red Hat Software","jSPs","PeopleSoft","Sillicon Graphics"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d1"},"question":"What follows i. e.'s acquisition of Sun Microsystems on January 27,2010?","answer":"Oracle Corporation","sentence":"Oracle Corporation is the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform, following their acquisition of Sun Microsystems on January 27,2010.","score":"3.1258803625665967","choices":["Paul Sernoty Red Hat Software","David Hyland Intel","Oracle Corporation","George Flank Apple"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d2"},"question":"What did Sun Microsystems release as Java 1. 0 in 1996?","answer":"the first public implementation","sentence":"Sun Microsystems released the first public implementation as Java 1. 0 in 1996.","score":"3.1226808312438794","choices":["the third government implement","the second private implementing","the first public implementation","the fourth education implemented"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d3"},"question":"Who have developed alternative implementations for Java, GNU Classpath, and IcedTea-Web?","answer":"others","sentence":"Meanwhile, others have developed alternative implementations of these Sun technologies, such as the GNU Compiler for Java (bytecode compiler), GNU Classpath (standard libraries), and IcedTea-Web (browser plugin for applets).","score":"3.1192008447397908","choices":["many","others","some","other"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d4"},"question":"Who supplies the Java platform for use with Java?","answer":"Oracle","sentence":"Oracle supplies the Java platform for use with Java.","score":"3.1173775276059437","choices":["Michigan","Oracle","Colombia","Boston"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d5"},"question":"Who has support for desktop computers and web browsers on Microsoft Windows, Linux, and macOS?","answer":"JavaFX","sentence":"JavaFX has support for desktop computers and web browsers on Microsoft Windows, Linux, and macOS.","score":"3.1165474353604985","choices":["Phoenix","JavaFX","Bahrain","Colombia"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d6"},"question":"What had Sun relicensed under the GNU General Public License in compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process?","answer":"most of compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process's Java technologies","sentence":"As of May 2007, in compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process, Sun had relicensed most of its Java technologies under the GNU General Public License.","score":"3.1024658807729035","choices":["most of complying with the requirements of the Java Community Process's Java systems","most of compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process's Java technologies","most of comply with the specification of the Java Community Process's Java technology","most of implementation with the specified of the Java Community Process's Java innovations"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d7"},"question":"What did a San Francisco jury find by on May 7,2012?","answer":"that if APIs could be copyrighted, then Google had infringed Oracle's copyrights by the use of Java in Android devices","sentence":"On May 7,2012, a San Francisco jury found that if APIs could be copyrighted, then Google had infringed Oracle's copyrights by the use of Java in Android devices.","score":"3.1010777963377305","choices":["that if PeopleSoft would be copying, then Paul Sernoty had infringe peoplesoft's trademarks by the used of Java in Android device","that if APIs could be copyrighted, then Google had infringed Oracle's copyrights by the use of Java in Android devices","that if Red Hat Software if be infringing, then Robert Clinton had infringes ellison's copyrighted by the allow of Java in Android computers","that if SAP might be patents, then George Flank had infringing microsystems's patents by the using of Java in Android phones"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d8"},"question":"When did Sun Microsystems release the first public implementation as Java 1. 0?","answer":"in 1996","sentence":"Sun Microsystems released the first public implementation as Java 1. 0 in 1996.","score":"3.089981388865114","choices":["in 1997","in 1998","in 1995","in 1996"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571d9"},"question":"Whose copyrights did a San Francisco jury find by on May 7,2012?","answer":"that if APIs could be copyrighted, then Google had infringed Oracle's copyrights by the use of Java in Android devices","sentence":"On May 7,2012, a San Francisco jury found that if APIs could be copyrighted, then Google had infringed Oracle's copyrights by the use of Java in Android devices.","score":"3.0875504181904314","choices":["that if Intel if be infringing, then Paul Sernoty had infringes ellison's copyrighted by the allow of Java in Android computers","that if IBM might be patents, then David Hyland had infringing microsystems's patents by the using of Java in Android phones","that if APIs could be copyrighted, then Google had infringed Oracle's copyrights by the use of Java in Android devices","that if Apple would be copying, then Johann Carry had infringe peoplesoft's trademarks by the used of Java in Android device"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571da"},"question":"Who does Oracle Corporation follow i. e.'s acquisition of on January 27,2010?","answer":"of Sun Microsystems","sentence":"Oracle Corporation is the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform, following their acquisition of Sun Microsystems on January 27,2010.","score":"3.0815317778257434","choices":["of Apple","of Sun Microsystems","of AMD","of Best Buy"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571db"},"question":"What did Sun release much of November 13,2006's Java virtual machine as?","answer":"as free and open-source software","sentence":"On November 13,2006, Sun released much of its Java virtual machine as free and open-source software, under the terms of the GNU General Public License.","score":"3.0704708119636575","choices":["as without and cross-platform microsoft","as available and implementations hardware","as free and open-source software","as freedom and gpl computer"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571dc"},"question":"What did the Appeals Court send down?","answer":"the case of determining the damages to federal court in San Francisco","sentence":"On March 2018, this ruling was overturned by the Appeals Court, which sent down the case of determining the damages to federal court in San Francisco.","score":"3.066354372416201","choices":["the appeals of determines the damage to enforcement appeals in Richard Mccullam","the trial of determine the punitive to government judge in John Thomas","the case of determining the damages to federal court in San Francisco","the prosecutors of assessing the compensation to state supreme in Johann Carry"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571dd"},"question":"What does Oracle aim to replace with the Garbage-First Collector?","answer":"CMS","sentence":"Oracle aims to replace CMS with the Garbage-First Collector.","score":"3.063073182621218","choices":["CMS","Intel","PeopleSoft","IBM"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571de"},"question":"What had Sun relicensed most of compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process's Java technologies under the GNU General Public License in?","answer":"in compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process","sentence":"As of May 2007, in compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process, Sun had relicensed most of its Java technologies under the GNU General Public License.","score":"3.060828623640264","choices":["in implementation with the specified of the George Flank","in compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process","in comply with the specification of the William Maxwell","in complying with the requirements of the Paul Sernoty"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571df"},"question":"What did Sun also provide an edition called Personal Java that has been superseded by?","answer":"by later, standards-based Java ME configuration-profile pairings","sentence":"Sun also provided an edition called Personal Java that has been superseded by later, standards-based Java ME configuration-profile pairings.","score":"3.055915323715795","choices":["by subsequently, curricula John Thomas configuration-profile pairing","by then, technology-based William Maxwell configuration-profile foursomes","by later, standards-based Java ME configuration-profile pairings","by after, e-learning Richard Mccullam configuration-profile matchups"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e0"},"question":"What did the Java servlet API has to some extent been supersede by:?","answer":"by two standard Java technologies for web services","sentence":"The Java servlet API has to some extent been superseded by two standard Java technologies for web services:","score":"3.0513363754250964","choices":["by two standard Java technologies for web services","by four example C++ systems for online provider","by five basic Python innovations for website providers","by three definition C technology for internet service"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e1"},"question":"What was overturned by the Appeals Court on March 2018?","answer":"this ruling","sentence":"On March 2018, this ruling was overturned by the Appeals Court, which sent down the case of determining the damages to federal court in San Francisco.","score":"3.050959227186422","choices":["this ruled","this court","this supreme","this ruling"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e2"},"question":"Who does Java servlet technology provide with a simple, consistent mechanism for extending the functionality of a Web server and for accessing existing business systems?","answer":"Web developers","sentence":"Java servlet technology provides Web developers with a simple, consistent mechanism for extending the functionality of a Web server and for accessing existing business systems.","score":"3.0166621268063984","choices":["internet developer","website software","online builders","Web developers"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e3"},"question":"Who also provided an edition called Personal Java that has been superseded by later, standards-based Java ME configuration-profile pairings?","answer":"Sun","sentence":"Sun also provided an edition called Personal Java that has been superseded by later, standards-based Java ME configuration-profile pairings.","score":"3.0157615730923064","choices":["Sun","moon","sunlight","microsystems"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e4"},"question":"What did Sun release as free and open-source software?","answer":"much of November 13,2006's Java virtual machine","sentence":"On November 13,2006, Sun released much of its Java virtual machine as free and open-source software, under the terms of the GNU General Public License.","score":"3.011875735842332","choices":["even of october 13,2006's C cyberspace automatic","less of february 13,2006's Python simulation guns","much of November 13,2006's Java virtual machine","than of december 13,2006's C++ online gun"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e5"},"question":"What constitutes fair use on May 26,2016?","answer":"the district court decided in favor of Google","sentence":"On May 26,2016, the district court decided in favor of Google, ruling the copyright infringement of the Java API in Android constitutes fair use.","score":"3.0108596603643134","choices":["the area supreme decision in favoring of Richard Mccullam","the village appeals would in favored of Paul Sernoty","the district court decided in favor of Google","the county judge decide in favour of John Thomas"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e6"},"question":"Who are server-side Java EE components that generate responses to requests from clients?","answer":"servlets","sentence":"Servlets are server-side Java EE components that generate responses (typically HTML pages) to requests (typically HTTP requests) from clients.","score":"3.009967456233206","choices":["javaserver","servlet","javabeans","servlets"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e7"},"question":"Who is essential to Java EE?","answer":"Platform-independent Java","sentence":"Platform-independent Java is essential to Java EE, and an even more rigorous validation is required to certify an implementation.","score":"3.009194097105152","choices":["cross-platform C++","Platform-independent Java","vendor-neutral Python","platform-specific C"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e8"},"question":"What provides Web developers with a simple, consistent mechanism for extending the functionality of a Web server and for accessing existing business systems?","answer":"Java servlet technology","sentence":"Java servlet technology provides Web developers with a simple, consistent mechanism for extending the functionality of a Web server and for accessing existing business systems.","score":"3.0080003977896825","choices":["C++ jsp tech","Python tomcat technological","C ejb technologies","Java servlet technology"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571e9"},"question":"When is the Java applet API now deprecated since Java 9?","answer":"in 2017","sentence":"The Java applet API is now deprecated since Java 9 in 2017.","score":"3.006841882601737","choices":["in 2015","in 2019","in 2016","in 2017"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ea"},"question":"What is a graphical user interface library for the Java SE platform?","answer":"swing","sentence":"Swing is a graphical user interface library for the Java SE platform.","score":"3.0047647774421016","choices":["pendulum","swinging","swung","swing"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571eb"},"question":"Who is Oracle Corporation?","answer":"the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform","sentence":"Oracle Corporation is the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform, following their acquisition of Sun Microsystems on January 27,2010.","score":"2.9990170517175017","choices":["the the owns of the according implement of the Charles Page framework","the its proprietor of the saying implemented of the William Maxwell support","the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform","the present owned of the ministry implementing of the David Hyland supports"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ec"},"question":"What did Sun release much of as free and open-source software?","answer":"of November 13,2006's Java virtual machine","sentence":"On November 13,2006, Sun released much of its Java virtual machine as free and open-source software, under the terms of the GNU General Public License.","score":"2.995380883137295","choices":["of November 13,2006's Java virtual machine","of october 13,2006's C cyberspace automatic","of december 13,2006's C++ online gun","of february 13,2006's Python simulation guns"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ed"},"question":"When were just-in-time compilers that compile byte-codes to machine code during runtime introduced?","answer":"from an early stage","sentence":"Just-in-time compilers that compile byte-codes to machine code during runtime were introduced from an early stage.","score":"2.987653303282518","choices":["from an later staging","from an earlier phase","from an early stage","from an late theater"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ee"},"question":"Who claimed that the Microsoft implementation did not support RMI or JNI?","answer":"Sun","sentence":"This resulted in a legal dispute with Microsoft after Sun claimed that the Microsoft implementation did not support RMI or JNI and had added platform-specific features of their own.","score":"2.9862487677431977","choices":["moon","sunlight","Sun","microsystems"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ef"},"question":"What is incompatible with Java bytecode?","answer":"the bytecode language supported by the Android SDK","sentence":"The bytecode language supported by the Android SDK is incompatible with Java bytecode and runs on its own virtual machine, optimized for low-memory devices such as smartphones and tablet computers.","score":"2.970768983515679","choices":["the p-code word opposed by the David Hyland","the jvm arabic support by the Richard Mccullam","the runtime english supports by the William Maxwell","the bytecode language supported by the Android SDK"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f0"},"question":"Who initiated the Java language project in June 1991?","answer":"James Gosling, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton","sentence":"James Gosling, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton initiated the Java language project in June 1991.","score":"2.969168261865687","choices":["Robert Clinton phillippe, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton","Paul Sernoty callum, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton","Richard Mccullam ryan, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton","James Gosling, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton"],"difficulty":"E","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f1"},"question":"What are Java applications typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine regardless of?","answer":"of the underlying computer architecture","sentence":"Java applications are typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine regardless of the underlying computer architecture.","score":"2.9691668223832033","choices":["of the factors technology gothic","of the fundamentals pc design","of the underlying computer architecture","of the fundamental software architectural"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f2"},"question":"When does the district court decided in favor of Google constitute fair use?","answer":"on May 26,2016","sentence":"On May 26,2016, the district court decided in favor of Google, ruling the copyright infringement of the Java API in Android constitutes fair use.","score":"2.964767451180322","choices":["on May 26,2016","on might 26,2016","on likely 26,2016","on could 26,2016"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f3"},"question":"Who ruled on May 31 that APIs cannot be copyrighted?","answer":"District Judge William Haskell Alsup","sentence":"District Judge William Haskell Alsup ruled on May 31,2012, that APIs cannot be copyrighted, but this was reversed by the United States Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit in May 2014.","score":"2.96240361893713","choices":["Montana appeals George Flank","Phoenix judges William Maxwell","District Judge William Haskell Alsup","America court James Hockey"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f4"},"question":"Who is swing controlled by in cooperation with others through the Java Community Process program?","answer":"by Sun Microsystems","sentence":"It is controlled by Sun Microsystems in cooperation with others through the Java Community Process program.","score":"2.9618120009853626","choices":["by SAP","by Sillicon Graphics","by Nvidia","by Sun Microsystems"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f5"},"question":"What does Oracle follow Oracle Corporation's acquisition of in 200910?","answer":"of Sun Microsystems","sentence":"Following Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems in 200910, Oracle has described itself as the steward of Java technology with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency.","score":"2.959356267209628","choices":["of IBM","of Sun Microsystems","of AMD","of PeopleSoft"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f6"},"question":"What is that programmers can be spared the burden of having to perform manual memory management?","answer":"one of the ideas behind Java's automatic memory management model","sentence":"One of the ideas behind Java's automatic memory management model is that programmers can be spared the burden of having to perform manual memory management.","score":"2.9591933473859955","choices":["three of the theories second Python's automated remembering asset design","only of the concepts third C++'s automatically dram managing modeling","another of the idea ahead C's machine memories managers concept","one of the ideas behind Java's automatic memory management model"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f7"},"question":"What did the use of Java-related technology in Android lead to?","answer":"to a legal dispute between Oracle and Google","sentence":"The use of Java-related technology in Android led to a legal dispute between Oracle and Google.","score":"2.952919292259771","choices":["to a constitutional resolved between Oracle and Google","to a lawyers disputed between Oracle and Google","to a law resolve between Oracle and Google","to a legal dispute between Oracle and Google"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f8"},"question":"What does the Java programming language require the presence of?","answer":"of a software platform in order for compiled programs to be executed","sentence":"The Java programming language requires the presence of a software platform in order for compiled programs to be executed.","score":"2.947828023810179","choices":["of a microsoft framework in to for compile programmes to be executing","of a software platform in order for compiled programs to be executed","of a computer supports in ordered for compiling program to be execution","of a hardware support in must for collected educational to be execute"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571f9"},"question":"What is either interpreted by the Dalvik virtual machine or compiled into native code by the Android Runtime?","answer":"the bytecode","sentence":"Depending on the Android version, the bytecode is either interpreted by the Dalvik virtual machine or compiled into native code by the Android Runtime.","score":"2.9434656427489982","choices":["the p-code","the bytecode","the runtime","the jvm"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571fa"},"question":"What is to make all implementations of Java compatible?","answer":"the goal of Java","sentence":"The goal of Java is to make all implementations of Java compatible.","score":"2.9432679490876517","choices":["the scoring of C++","the goal of Java","the scored of C","the kick of Python"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571fb"},"question":"Who approached the ISO\\/IEC JTC 1 standards body and later the Ecma International to formalize Java in 1997?","answer":"Sun Microsystems","sentence":"In 1997, Sun Microsystems approached the ISO\\/IEC JTC 1 standards body and later the Ecma International to formalize Java, but it soon withdrew from the process.","score":"2.9362681225310503","choices":["Sillicon Graphics","SAP","IBM","Sun Microsystems"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571fc"},"question":"Who were originally released by Sun under proprietary licenses?","answer":"the original and reference implementation Java compilers, virtual machines, and class libraries","sentence":"The original and reference implementation Java compilers, virtual machines, and class libraries were originally released by Sun under proprietary licenses.","score":"2.9347184512446565","choices":["the version and description implementing C compiler, cyberspace machine, and classes library","the versions and referring implemented Python c++, simulation vending, and school librarians","the original and reference implementation Java compilers, virtual machines, and class libraries","the originally and refers implement C++ implementations, online computers, and type museums"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571fd"},"question":"What released much of November 13,2006's Java virtual machine as free and open-source software?","answer":"Sun","sentence":"On November 13,2006, Sun released much of its Java virtual machine as free and open-source software, under the terms of the GNU General Public License.","score":"2.9284549436511247","choices":["moon","microsystems","sunlight","Sun"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571fe"},"question":"When did District Judge William Haskell Alsup rule that APIs cannot be copyrighted?","answer":"on May 31","sentence":"District Judge William Haskell Alsup ruled on May 31,2012, that APIs cannot be copyrighted, but this was reversed by the United States Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit in May 2014.","score":"2.9089150863262065","choices":["on likely 27","on could 29","on might 28","on May 31"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b42571ff"},"question":"Who follows Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems in 200910?","answer":"Oracle","sentence":"Following Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems in 200910, Oracle has described itself as the steward of Java technology with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency.","score":"2.906899305445356","choices":["Oracle","Michigan","America","Phoenix"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257200"},"question":"What is now deprecated since Java 9 in 2017?","answer":"the Java applet API","sentence":"The Java applet API is now deprecated since Java 9 in 2017.","score":"2.905945024510266","choices":["the C++ dialer PeopleSoft","the C activex Intel","the Java applet API","the Python eprom SAP"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257201"},"question":"What lacks any formal standardization recognized by Ecma International, ISO\\/IEC, ANSI, or other third-party standards organization?","answer":"Java","sentence":"Because Java lacks any formal standardization recognized by Ecma International, ISO\\/IEC, ANSI, or other third-party standards organization, the Oracle implementation is the de facto standard.","score":"2.9045985373234253","choices":["Python","C","C++","Java"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257202"},"question":"What did Oracle announce in January 2016?","answer":"that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue the browser plugin","sentence":"In January 2016, Oracle announced that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue the browser plugin.","score":"2.8959285916580133","choices":["that Python compiler settings group on PeopleSoft 6 will suspend the microsoft sdk","that C++ statically ecosystems which on Nvidia 8 will discontinued the firefox add-on","that Java run-time environments based on JDK 9 will discontinue the browser plugin","that C compile-time environment company on Intel 7 will discontinuing the netscape javascript"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257203"},"question":"When was the type system of Java proven unsound?","answer":"in 2016","sentence":"In 2016, the type system of Java was proven unsound.","score":"2.893306085197339","choices":["in 2014","in 2015","in 2016","in 2018"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257204"},"question":"Whose acquisition of Sun Microsystems does Oracle follow in 200910?","answer":"Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems","sentence":"Following Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems in 200910, Oracle has described itself as the steward of Java technology with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency.","score":"2.892092001179179","choices":["David Hyland Intel's merger of Red Hat Software","Paul Sernoty Apple's purchase of Intel","Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems","William Maxwell IBM's acquire of PeopleSoft"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257205"},"question":"What does the district court decided in favor of Google constitute on May 26,2016?","answer":"fair use","sentence":"On May 26,2016, the district court decided in favor of Google, ruling the copyright infringement of the Java API in Android constitutes fair use.","score":"2.8904978794385325","choices":["honest using","ensure allow","reasonable used","fair use"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257206"},"question":"When does Oracle Corporation follow i. e.'s acquisition of Sun Microsystems?","answer":"on January 27,2010","sentence":"Oracle Corporation is the current owner of the official implementation of the Java SE platform, following their acquisition of Sun Microsystems on January 27,2010.","score":"2.8897100406237164","choices":["on october 27,2010","on december 27,2010","on february 27,2010","on January 27,2010"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257207"},"question":"What is based on the original implementation of Java by Sun?","answer":"this implementation","sentence":"This implementation is based on the original implementation of Java by Sun.","score":"2.887199597705709","choices":["this implementation","this implement","this implementing","this implemented"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257208"},"question":"What was Java released in 1995 as?","answer":"as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform","sentence":"Java was originally developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems (which has since been acquired by Oracle) and released in 1995 as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform.","score":"2.886075671994374","choices":["as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform","as a focus element of Sun Microsystems ' Java supports","as a basic essential of Sun Microsystems ' Java framework","as a underlying indicator of Sun Microsystems ' Java support"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257209"},"question":"What does game console to scientific supercomputers Java software runs on?","answer":"on everything from laptops to data centers","sentence":"Java software runs on everything from laptops to data centers, game consoles to scientific supercomputers.","score":"2.882844620945114","choices":["on else from phones to analysis clinics","on everything from laptops to data centers","on things from laptop to information centres","on everyone from cellphones to database center"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425720a"},"question":"What translates the Java bytecode into the platform's machine language?","answer":"the Java virtual machine for the overhead of interpreting bytecode into machine instructions","sentence":"Java itself is platform-independent and is adapted to the particular platform it is to run on by a Java virtual machine for it, which translates the Java bytecode into the platform's machine language.","score":"2.878103869928241","choices":["the C cyberspace automatic for the circled of interpret jvm into automatic instruction","the Java virtual machine for the overhead of interpreting bytecode into machine instructions","the Python simulation guns for the buzzed of interpretation runtime into guns orders","the C++ online gun for the circling of translating p-code into gun directives"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425720b"},"question":"What have others developed for Java, GNU Classpath, and IcedTea-Web?","answer":"alternative implementations","sentence":"Meanwhile, others have developed alternative implementations of these Sun technologies, such as the GNU Compiler for Java (bytecode compiler), GNU Classpath (standard libraries), and IcedTea-Web (browser plugin for applets).","score":"2.8765581539315863","choices":["alternate interfaces","ways compilers","alternative implementations","viable architectures"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425720c"},"question":"Who did Sun's vice-president Rich Green say that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as?","answer":"as an evangelist","sentence":"Sun's vice-president Rich Green said that Sun's ideal role with regard to Java was as an evangelist.","score":"2.87370923209112","choices":["as an televangelist","as an evangelist","as an evangelical","as an preacher"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425720d"},"question":"Who generated revenue from Java through the selling of licenses for specialized products such as the Java Enterprise System?","answer":"Sun","sentence":"Sun generated revenue from Java through the selling of licenses for specialized products such as the Java Enterprise System.","score":"2.8733777344863847","choices":["sunlight","microsystems","moon","Sun"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425720e"},"question":"Where was the Java 1. 0 compiler re-written by Arthur van Hoff to comply strictly with the Java 1. 0 language specification?","answer":"in Java","sentence":"The Java 1. 0 compiler was re-written in Java by Arthur van Hoff to comply strictly with the Java 1. 0 language specification.","score":"2.872921786311122","choices":["in Python","in C","in Java","in C++"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425720f"},"question":"What did Sun Microsystems release the first public implementation as in 1996?","answer":"as Java 1. 0","sentence":"Sun Microsystems released the first public implementation as Java 1. 0 in 1996.","score":"2.8715704571361558","choices":["as Java 1. 0","as C 2. 2","as Python 4. 3","as C++ 3. 1"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257210"},"question":"Who were added to the Java language in 2004?","answer":"generics","sentence":"In 2004, generics were added to the Java language, as part of J2SE 5. 0.","score":"2.869845752868504","choices":["generics","drugmakers","generic","ranbaxy"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257211"},"question":"Who advises Java's users to immediately transition to the latest version or an LTS release?","answer":"Oracle","sentence":"Since Java 9 (and 10 and 12) is no longer supported, Oracle advises its users to immediately transition to the latest version (currently Java 13) or an LTS release.","score":"2.8669938590192245","choices":["Michigan","Oracle","Bahrain","San Antonio"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257212"},"question":"What was the language initially called after an oak tree that stood outside Gosling's office?","answer":"Oak","sentence":"The language was initially called Oak after an oak tree that stood outside Gosling's office.","score":"2.866335688892993","choices":["Bahrain","Oak","Colombia","San Antonio"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257213"},"question":"Who was re-written in Java by Arthur van Hoff to comply strictly with the Java 1. 0 language specification?","answer":"the Java 1. 0 compiler","sentence":"The Java 1. 0 compiler was re-written in Java by Arthur van Hoff to comply strictly with the Java 1. 0 language specification.","score":"2.862167779695018","choices":["the Python 4. 3 implementations","the C++ 3. 1 fortran","the C 2. 2 c++","the Java 1. 0 compiler"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257214"},"question":"What is Platform-independent Java essential to?","answer":"to Java EE","sentence":"Platform-independent Java is essential to Java EE, and an even more rigorous validation is required to certify an implementation.","score":"2.862017097738525","choices":["to C lihn","to C++ sah","to Python uh","to Java EE"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257215"},"question":"Who made most of the time's Java implementations available without charge?","answer":"Sun","sentence":"At one time, Sun made most of its Java implementations available without charge, despite their proprietary software status.","score":"2.8605931299343164","choices":["Sun","sunlight","moon","microsystems"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257216"},"question":"What did jSPs embed Java code in by using the special delimiters?","answer":"in an HTML page","sentence":"JSPs embed Java code in an HTML page by using the special delimiters (% and %).","score":"2.860177336232782","choices":["in an Montana article","in an HTML page","in an San Antonio web","in an Germany editorial"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257217"},"question":"What did jSPs embed in an HTML page by using the special delimiters?","answer":"Java code","sentence":"JSPs embed Java code in an HTML page by using the special delimiters (% and %).","score":"2.8562960784551295","choices":["Python regulations","C rules","C++ penal","Java code"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257218"},"question":"What superseded by two standard Java technologies for web services:?","answer":"the Java servlet API has to some extent been","sentence":"The Java servlet API has to some extent been superseded by two standard Java technologies for web services:","score":"2.848117897904818","choices":["the C ejb Best Buy has to some scope been","the Python tomcat SAP has to some fact been","the C++ jsp Nvidia has to some severity been","the Java servlet API has to some extent been"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257219"},"question":"What does Swing in Java SE 6 address by using more native GUI widget drawing routines of the underlying platforms?","answer":"this problem","sentence":"Where prior implementations of these looks and feels may have been considered lacking, Swing in Java SE 6 addresses this problem by using more native GUI widget drawing routines of the underlying platforms.","score":"2.836886551634158","choices":["this problem","this solve","this serious","this trouble"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425721a"},"question":"What is a Java application in a JSP's own right?","answer":"the Java servlet","sentence":"A JSP is compiled to a Java servlet, a Java application in its own right, the first time it is accessed.","score":"2.8356554335113975","choices":["the C++ jsp","the C ejb","the Python tomcat","the Java servlet"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425721b"},"question":"Who does Oracle advise to immediately transition to the latest version or an LTS release?","answer":"Java's users","sentence":"Since Java 9 (and 10 and 12) is no longer supported, Oracle advises its users to immediately transition to the latest version (currently Java 13) or an LTS release.","score":"2.8354449613755897","choices":["C++'s internet","Java's users","C's user","Python's download"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425721c"},"question":"What is one of the ideas behind Java's automatic memory management model that programmers can be spared?","answer":"the burden of having to perform manual memory management","sentence":"One of the ideas behind Java's automatic memory management model is that programmers can be spared the burden of having to perform manual memory management.","score":"2.8322078419562944","choices":["the enormous of having to required 6-speed remembering asset","the onerous of having to performing five-speed dram managing","the burdened of having to performed 5-speed memories managers","the burden of having to perform manual memory management"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425721d"},"question":"What are organized into separate groups called packages?","answer":"the classes in the Java APIs","sentence":"The classes in the Java APIs are organized into separate groups called packages.","score":"2.831656035412598","choices":["the classes in the Java APIs","the students in the William Maxwell","the courses in the James Hockey","the class in the Richard Mccullam"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425721e"},"question":"Who are clones of Windows, GTK +, and Motif supplied by?","answer":"by Sun","sentence":"Clones of Windows, GTK +, and Motif are supplied by Sun.","score":"2.8245139288704815","choices":["by Sun","by sunlight","by microsystems","by moon"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425721f"},"question":"What renamed new J2 versions as Java EE, Java ME, and Java SE?","answer":"Sun","sentence":"In 2006, for marketing purposes, Sun renamed new J2 versions as Java EE, Java ME, and Java SE, respectively.","score":"2.8225974543307175","choices":["Sun","moon","sunlight","microsystems"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257220"},"question":"What had Sun relicensed most of under the GNU General Public License in compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process?","answer":"of compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process's Java technologies","sentence":"As of May 2007, in compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process, Sun had relicensed most of its Java technologies under the GNU General Public License.","score":"2.8214119555901043","choices":["of compliance with the specifications of the Java Community Process's Java technologies","of implementation with the specified of the Java Community Process's Java innovations","of complying with the requirements of the Java Community Process's Java systems","of comply with the specification of the Java Community Process's Java technology"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257221"},"question":"What is a key pillar in Android?","answer":"the Java language","sentence":"The Java language is a key pillar in Android, an open source mobile operating system.","score":"2.8205371566144355","choices":["the C++ word","the C arabic","the Java language","the Python english"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257222"},"question":"What is referenced as args although any other legal identifier name can be used by convention?","answer":"an explicit destructor method","sentence":"By convention, it is referenced as args although any other legal identifier name can be used.","score":"2.816417022532338","choices":["an suggestive spermatogonia techniques","an implicit varroa technique","an explicit destructor method","an references pheochromocytoma using"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257223"},"question":"What does the bytecode language supported by the Android SDK run on?","answer":"on its own virtual machine","sentence":"The bytecode language supported by the Android SDK is incompatible with Java bytecode and runs on its own virtual machine, optimized for low-memory devices such as smartphones and tablet computers.","score":"2.813426561384687","choices":["on its own simulation guns","on its own cyberspace automatic","on its own online gun","on its own virtual machine"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257224"},"question":"What did new versions have with the advent of Java 2?","answer":"multiple configurations built for different types of platforms","sentence":"With the advent of Java 2 (released initially as J2SE 1. 2 in December 1998 1999), new versions had multiple configurations built for different types of platforms.","score":"2.8132570232971252","choices":["numerous configuration constructed for various type of platform","multiple configurations built for different types of platforms","various subsystems building for these kinds of rigs","variety variants build for variety variety of terminals"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257225"},"question":"What means that programs written for the Java platform must run similarly on any combination of hardware and operating system with adequate run time support?","answer":"portability","sentence":"One design goal of Java is portability, which means that programs written for the Java platform must run similarly on any combination of hardware and operating system with adequate run time support.","score":"2.8089828425513077","choices":["accessibility","portability","hipaa","scalability"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257226"},"question":"When were generics added to the Java language?","answer":"in 2004","sentence":"In 2004, generics were added to the Java language, as part of J2SE 5. 0.","score":"2.806349736709646","choices":["in 2004","in 2006","in 2005","in 2003"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257227"},"question":"What is optimized for low-memory devices such as smartphones and tablet computers?","answer":"Java's own virtual machine","sentence":"The bytecode language supported by the Android SDK is incompatible with Java bytecode and runs on its own virtual machine, optimized for low-memory devices such as smartphones and tablet computers.","score":"2.8034624480060075","choices":["C's own cyberspace automatic","C++'s own online gun","Python's own simulation guns","Java's own virtual machine"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257228"},"question":"What is controlled through the Java Community Process?","answer":"the de facto standard","sentence":"Java remains a de facto standard, controlled through the Java Community Process.","score":"2.7994579149231087","choices":["the la defacto definition","the de facto standard","the y ipso basic","the en jure example"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257229"},"question":"What must accept an array of String objects?","answer":"the main method","sentence":"The main method must accept an array of String objects.","score":"2.7964081623810984","choices":["the key technique","the main method","the major techniques","the primary using"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425722a"},"question":"What launches Java by loading a given class?","answer":"the Java launcher","sentence":"The Java launcher launches Java by loading a given class (specified on the command line or as an attribute in a JAR) and starting its public static void main method.","score":"2.7951261890879384","choices":["the Java launcher","the C++ rocket","the Python grenades","the C grenade"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425722b"},"question":"What promised Write Once providing no-cost run-times on popular platforms?","answer":"the first public implementation","sentence":"It promised Write Once, Run Anywhere, providing no-cost run-times on popular platforms.","score":"2.7915466687177743","choices":["the fourth education implemented","the second private implementing","the third government implement","the first public implementation"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425722c"},"question":"Who has Oracle described Oracle Corporation's acquisition of as the steward of Java technology with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency?","answer":"of Sun Microsystems","sentence":"Following Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems in 200910, Oracle has described itself as the steward of Java technology with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency.","score":"2.791432800031698","choices":["of Sun Microsystems","of Sillicon Graphics","of Red Hat Software","of Apple"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425722d"},"question":"What browsers soon incorporated the ability to run Java applets within web pages?","answer":"major web","sentence":"Major web browsers soon incorporated the ability to run Java applets within web pages, and Java quickly became popular.","score":"2.786755512542223","choices":["significant online","main website","major web","biggest internet"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425722e"},"question":"When did James Gosling, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton initiate the Java language project?","answer":"in June 1991","sentence":"James Gosling, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton initiated the Java language project in June 1991.","score":"2.7858130678025095","choices":["in july 1992","in october 1993","in april 1990","in June 1991"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425722f"},"question":"Who allow compile-time type checking without having to create many container classes?","answer":"generics","sentence":"Generics allow compile-time type checking without having to create many container classes, each containing almost identical code.","score":"2.7846714076403707","choices":["ranbaxy","drugmakers","generic","generics"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257230"},"question":"What are Java applications typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine?","answer":"regardless of the underlying computer architecture","sentence":"Java applications are typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine regardless of the underlying computer architecture.","score":"2.784559893593851","choices":["determine of the factors technology gothic","irrespective of the fundamental software architectural","whatever of the fundamentals pc design","regardless of the underlying computer architecture"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257231"},"question":"What is swing controlled by Sun Microsystems in cooperation with others through?","answer":"through the Java Community Process program","sentence":"It is controlled by Sun Microsystems in cooperation with others through the Java Community Process program.","score":"2.77980443854968","choices":["through the C++ AMD negotiations programmes","through the Python Best Buy implementation education","through the Java Community Process program","through the C Sillicon Graphics processes programme"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257232"},"question":"What did Sun claim that the Microsoft implementation did not support?","answer":"RMI or JNI","sentence":"This resulted in a legal dispute with Microsoft after Sun claimed that the Microsoft implementation did not support RMI or JNI and had added platform-specific features of their own.","score":"2.7708125388452696","choices":["AMD or Best Buy","Best Buy or AMD","RMI or JNI","Red Hat Software or PeopleSoft"],"difficulty":"M","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257233"},"question":"What is the Java applet API now deprecated since in 2017?","answer":"since Java 9","sentence":"The Java applet API is now deprecated since Java 9 in 2017.","score":"2.769326661318675","choices":["since Java 9","ago Python 6","last C 7","years C++ 8"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257234"},"question":"What do Oracle (and others) highly recommend uninstalling because of serious risks due to unresolved security issues?","answer":"older versions of Java","sentence":"Oracle (and others) highly recommend uninstalling older versions of Java because of serious risks due to unresolved security issues.","score":"2.757238114941389","choices":["older versions of Java","newer newer of Python","age variants of C++","younger version of C"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257235"},"question":"What uses the parallel scavenge garbage collector by default?","answer":"HotSpot","sentence":"By default, HotSpot uses the parallel scavenge garbage collector.","score":"2.7548806734695996","choices":["Red Hat Software","Nvidia","PeopleSoft","HotSpot"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257236"},"question":"What can influence the design and development of the APIs?","answer":"companies or individuals participating in this process","sentence":"Companies or individuals participating in this process can influence the design and development of the APIs.","score":"2.74906622905334","choices":["companies or individuals participating in this process","company or those participation in this implementation","firms or persons participate in this processes","businesses or individual participated in this negotiations"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257237"},"question":"What does the Java programming language require?","answer":"the presence of a software platform in order for compiled programs to be executed","sentence":"The Java programming language requires the presence of a software platform in order for compiled programs to be executed.","score":"2.7462395979686796","choices":["the presence of a software platform in order for compiled programs to be executed","the absence of a microsoft framework in to for compile programmes to be executing","the forces of a hardware support in must for collected educational to be execute","the force of a computer supports in ordered for compiling program to be execution"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257238"},"question":"Who is sufficient for 90 % of applications in Java?","answer":"the Concurrent Mark-Sweep garbage collector","sentence":"For 90 % of applications in Java, the Concurrent Mark-Sweep garbage collector is sufficient.","score":"2.744047047674143","choices":["the sr Mark-Sweep waste dealer","the concurrently Mark-Sweep trash connoisseur","the concurrency Mark-Sweep rubbish collection","the Concurrent Mark-Sweep garbage collector"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257239"},"question":"What is the name Green simply the name of the method calls to pass control to the program?","answer":"the Java launcher","sentence":"It is simply the name of the method the Java launcher calls to pass control to the program.","score":"2.7346337706964516","choices":["the Java launcher","the C++ rocket","the Python grenades","the C grenade"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425723a"},"question":"What are typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine regardless of the underlying computer architecture?","answer":"Java applications","sentence":"Java applications are typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine regardless of the underlying computer architecture.","score":"2.7341201731871476","choices":["C++ software","Python devices","Java applications","C application"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425723b"},"question":"What are Java applications typically compiled to bytecode that can run on regardless of the underlying computer architecture?","answer":"on any Java virtual machine","sentence":"Java applications are typically compiled to bytecode that can run on any Java virtual machine regardless of the underlying computer architecture.","score":"2.7314976612555664","choices":["on any C cyberspace automatic","on any Java virtual machine","on any Python simulation guns","on any C++ online gun"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425723c"},"question":"What do Oracle (and others) highly recommend uninstalling older versions of Java because of?","answer":"because of serious risks due to unresolved security issues","sentence":"Oracle (and others) highly recommend uninstalling older versions of Java because of serious risks due to unresolved security issues.","score":"2.7302099622234404","choices":["because of problem danger because to thorny intelligence topics","because of severe dangers result to unsolved military matters","because of problems risk owing to disputes forces issue","because of serious risks due to unresolved security issues"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425723d"},"question":"What does the out object provide for printing data to standard out, including println which also appends a new line to the passed string?","answer":"many methods","sentence":"The out object is an instance of the PrintStream class and provides many methods for printing data to standard out, including println which also appends a new line to the passed string.","score":"2.729400839577214","choices":["several technique","many methods","few method","some techniques"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425723e"},"question":"What is developed to support application development in Java?","answer":"the standard library","sentence":"The Java Class Library is the standard library, developed to support application development in Java.","score":"2.729103760973978","choices":["the basic archive","the definition libraries","the example archives","the standard library"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425723f"},"question":"What were programs that were embedded in other applications?","answer":"Java applets","sentence":"Java applets were programs that were embedded in other applications, typically in a Web page displayed in a web browser.","score":"2.725257607554044","choices":["Python javascript","C applet","C++ activex","Java applets"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257240"},"question":"What provide a generic way to access host-specific features such as graphics, threading, and networking?","answer":"Standard libraries","sentence":"Standard libraries provide a generic way to access host-specific features such as graphics, threading, and networking.","score":"2.719381585563739","choices":["standards library","example librarians","definition museums","Standard libraries"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257241"},"question":"What does Sun's trademark license for usage of the Java brand insist?","answer":"that all implementations be compatible","sentence":"Historically, Sun's trademark license for usage of the Java brand insists that all implementations be compatible.","score":"2.7164613146343437","choices":["that all implementations be compatible","that all interfaces be compatibility","that all architectures be incompatible","that all compilers be pcs"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257242"},"question":"What does not provide the full Java SE standard library?","answer":"Android","sentence":"Android does not provide the full Java SE standard library, although the Android SDK does include an independent implementation of a large subset of it.","score":"2.715150819934626","choices":["Michigan","Phoenix","Android","America"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257243"},"question":"Who is an explicit destructor method referenced as although any other legal identifier name can be used by convention?","answer":"as args","sentence":"By convention, it is referenced as args although any other legal identifier name can be used.","score":"2.7089148915971655","choices":["as args","as mmos","as 7.7997","as isvs"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257244"},"question":"What uses an automatic garbage collector to manage memory in the object lifecycle?","answer":"Java","sentence":"Java uses an automatic garbage collector to manage memory in the object lifecycle.","score":"2.7027654456549683","choices":["Java","Python","C","C++"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257245"},"question":"What is available for Microsoft Windows, macOS, Linux, and Solaris?","answer":"the Oracle implementation","sentence":"The Oracle implementation is available for Microsoft Windows (still works for XP, while only later versions are currently officially supported), macOS, Linux, and Solaris.","score":"2.7012393180865866","choices":["the Phoenix implement","the San Antonio implemented","the Germany implementing","the Oracle implementation"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257246"},"question":"What does the Java launcher launch by loading a given class?","answer":"Java","sentence":"The Java launcher launches Java by loading a given class (specified on the command line or as an attribute in a JAR) and starting its public static void main method.","score":"2.70089872569343","choices":["C","Java","Python","C++"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257247"},"question":"What had multiple configurations built for different types of platforms with the advent of Java 2?","answer":"new versions","sentence":"With the advent of Java 2 (released initially as J2SE 1. 2 in December 1998 1999), new versions had multiple configurations built for different types of platforms.","score":"2.700447448815808","choices":["first variants","same newer","new versions","york version"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257248"},"question":"Who release versions of Java:?","answer":"Major","sentence":"Major release versions of Java, along with their release dates:","score":"2.6990483264378753","choices":["Major","main","significant","biggest"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257249"},"question":"What does HotSpot use the parallel scavenge garbage collector by?","answer":"by default","sentence":"By default, HotSpot uses the parallel scavenge garbage collector.","score":"2.6982305582740835","choices":["by swaps","by default","by debt","by borrowers"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425724a"},"question":"What is simply the name of the method the Java launcher calls to pass control to the program?","answer":"the name Green","sentence":"It is simply the name of the method the Java launcher calls to pass control to the program.","score":"2.6972083767060284","choices":["the known blue","the named purple","the word red","the name Green"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425724b"},"question":"What does not have support for native OS look?","answer":"JavaFX","sentence":"JavaFX does not have support for native OS look and feels.","score":"2.696820649095183","choices":["Bahrain","San Antonio","JavaFX","Michigan"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425724c"},"question":"Who are supplied by Sun?","answer":"clones of Windows, GTK +, and Motif","sentence":"Clones of Windows, GTK +, and Motif are supplied by Sun.","score":"2.696586367348673","choices":["offspring of Windows, GTK +, and Motif","clones of Windows, GTK +, and Motif","cloned of Windows, GTK +, and Motif","clone of Windows, GTK +, and Motif"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425724d"},"question":"What insists that all implementations be compatible?","answer":"Sun's trademark license for usage of the Java brand","sentence":"Historically, Sun's trademark license for usage of the Java brand insists that all implementations be compatible.","score":"2.693998102370383","choices":["Sun's trademark license for usage of the Java brand","San Antonio's infringement licensing for e.g. of the Python marketing","Michigan's signature licences for refers of the C++ products","Montana's patent licence for use of the C product"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425724e"},"question":"What is compiled to a Java servlet?","answer":"a JSP","sentence":"A JSP is compiled to a Java servlet, a Java application in its own right, the first time it is accessed.","score":"2.684253971137909","choices":["a Red Hat Software","a JSP","a Apple","a Intel"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425724f"},"question":"What does portability mean that programs written for the Java platform must run similarly on?","answer":"on any combination of hardware and operating system with adequate run time support","sentence":"One design goal of Java is portability, which means that programs written for the Java platform must run similarly on any combination of hardware and operating system with adequate run time support.","score":"2.6831974338688447","choices":["on any unusual of computer and revenue control with inadequate go but backing","on any combination of hardware and operating system with adequate run time support","on any combined of pc and operations mechanism with insufficient ran before supporting","on any combining of software and operate which with sufficient running when supported"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257250"},"question":"What did James Gosling, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton initiate in June 1991?","answer":"the Java language project","sentence":"James Gosling, Mike Sheridan, and Patrick Naughton initiated the Java language project in June 1991.","score":"2.683061957502172","choices":["the Python english build","the C++ word construction","the C arabic development","the Java language project"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257251"},"question":"When Sun sued as well as a court order enforcing the terms of the license from Sun?","answer":"in 1997","sentence":"Sun sued in 1997, and, in 2001, won a settlement of US$20 million, as well as a court order enforcing the terms of the license from Sun.","score":"2.6807439212739426","choices":["in 1996","in 1998","in 1999","in 1997"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257252"},"question":"Who highly recommend uninstalling older versions of Java because of serious risks due to unresolved security issues?","answer":"Oracle (and others)","sentence":"Oracle (and others) highly recommend uninstalling older versions of Java because of serious risks due to unresolved security issues.","score":"2.6730475756201226","choices":["Germany (and many)","Oracle (and others)","Bahrain (and other)","Colombia (and some)"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257253"},"question":"What has Oracle described Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems as the steward of Java technology with?","answer":"with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency","sentence":"Following Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems in 200910, Oracle has described itself as the steward of Java technology with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency.","score":"2.6669147577648764","choices":["with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency","with a incessant determination to nurturing a organizations of participating and accountability","with a ferocious willingness to fostered a neighborhood of involvement and fairness","with a unrelenting pledge to promoting a communities of participate and openness"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257254"},"question":"What consoles to scientific supercomputers Java software runs on everything from laptops to data centers?","answer":"game","sentence":"Java software runs on everything from laptops to data centers, game consoles to scientific supercomputers.","score":"2.664091945583141","choices":["play","player","game","players"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257255"},"question":"What main is not a keyword in the Java language?","answer":"the method name","sentence":"The method name main is not a keyword in the Java language.","score":"2.6615121217587423","choices":["the technique word","the using named","the method name","the techniques known"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257256"},"question":"What does Java use an automatic garbage collector to manage in the object lifecycle?","answer":"memory","sentence":"Java uses an automatic garbage collector to manage memory in the object lifecycle.","score":"2.6612631953533996","choices":["memory","memories","remembering","dram"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257257"},"question":"What launches Java by starting the public class's public static void main method?","answer":"the Java launcher","sentence":"The Java launcher launches Java by loading a given class (specified on the command line or as an attribute in a JAR) and starting its public static void main method.","score":"2.6600308519252955","choices":["the Python grenades","the C++ rocket","the C grenade","the Java launcher"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257258"},"question":"What is possible to feel system of Swing?","answer":"swing","sentence":"It is possible to specify a different look and feel through the pluggable look and feel system of Swing.","score":"2.6539658553181704","choices":["swing","swinging","pendulum","swung"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257259"},"question":"Who does Java use to manage memory in the object lifecycle?","answer":"an automatic garbage collector","sentence":"Java uses an automatic garbage collector to manage memory in the object lifecycle.","score":"2.652356926721441","choices":["an machine trash connoisseur","an automatically rubbish collection","an automated waste dealer","an automatic garbage collector"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425725a"},"question":"What provides many methods for printing data to standard out, including println which also appends a new line to the passed string?","answer":"the out object","sentence":"The out object is an instance of the PrintStream class and provides many methods for printing data to standard out, including println which also appends a new line to the passed string.","score":"2.648822562084907","choices":["the out object","the out inanimate","the out element","the out particular"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425725b"},"question":"What are the classes in the Java APIs organized into?","answer":"into separate groups called packages","sentence":"The classes in the Java APIs are organized into separate groups called packages.","score":"2.648221097684743","choices":["into separate groups called packages","into separately group known package","into two organizations referred packaged","into three activists calling severance"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425725c"},"question":"What is an instance of the PrintStream class?","answer":"the out object","sentence":"The out object is an instance of the PrintStream class and provides many methods for printing data to standard out, including println which also appends a new line to the passed string.","score":"2.6438550104159764","choices":["the out inanimate","the out particular","the out object","the out element"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425725d"},"question":"What supports Java 6 and some Java 7 features?","answer":"Android","sentence":"It supports Java 6 and some Java 7 features, offering an implementation compatible with the standard library (Apache Harmony).","score":"2.6403038445022937","choices":["Android","San Antonio","America","Texas"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425725e"},"question":"What is an explicit destructor method referenced as args although any other legal identifier name can be used by?","answer":"by convention","sentence":"By convention, it is referenced as args although any other legal identifier name can be used.","score":"2.639678180529432","choices":["by delegates","by geneva","by conference","by convention"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425725f"},"question":"What does Java use an automatic garbage collector to manage memory in?","answer":"in the object lifecycle","sentence":"Java uses an automatic garbage collector to manage memory in the object lifecycle.","score":"2.637651128165442","choices":["in the particular end-to-end","in the element workflow","in the object lifecycle","in the inanimate plm"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257260"},"question":"What is the name Green simply the Java launcher calls to pass control to the program?","answer":"the name of the method","sentence":"It is simply the name of the method the Java launcher calls to pass control to the program.","score":"2.62730767724105","choices":["the known of the techniques","the name of the method","the word of the technique","the named of the using"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257261"},"question":"What did no longer ships java with Windows as?","answer":"as a result","sentence":"As a result, Microsoft no longer ships Java with Windows.","score":"2.6270965066952745","choices":["as a resulting","as a due","as a result","as a resulted"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257262"},"question":"What does Oracle supply?","answer":"the Java platform for use with Java","sentence":"Oracle supplies the Java platform for use with Java.","score":"2.6240698066204367","choices":["the Java platform for use with Java","the C++ framework for using with C++","the Python support for allow with Python","the C supports for used with C"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257263"},"question":"What was Java according to GitHub?","answer":"one of the most popular programming languages in use","sentence":"As of 2019, Java was one of the most popular programming languages in use according to GitHub, particularly for client-server web applications, with a reported 9 million developers.","score":"2.623628006222343","choices":["another of the most popularity broadcasts language in used","one of the most popular programming languages in use","only of the most most broadcast dialects in using","three of the most favorite programs spoken in allow"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257264"},"question":"What is the name Green simply the name of the method the Java launcher calls to pass control to?","answer":"to the program","sentence":"It is simply the name of the method the Java launcher calls to pass control to the program.","score":"2.6197937006912078","choices":["to the programmes","to the programme","to the education","to the program"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257265"},"question":"What did new versions have multiple configurations built for different types of platforms with?","answer":"with the advent of Java 2","sentence":"With the advent of Java 2 (released initially as J2SE 1. 2 in December 1998 1999), new versions had multiple configurations built for different types of platforms.","score":"2.619031310899876","choices":["with the advent of Java 2","with the introduction of C 3","with the emergence of C++ 4","with the twentieth of Python 1"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257266"},"question":"What is the name Green simply the name of the Java launcher calls to pass control to the program?","answer":"of the method","sentence":"It is simply the name of the method the Java launcher calls to pass control to the program.","score":"2.6130877252305815","choices":["of the technique","of the using","of the method","of the techniques"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257267"},"question":"What is a software platform for delivering desktop applications, as well as rich Internet applications that can run across a wide variety of devices?","answer":"JavaFX","sentence":"JavaFX is a software platform for creating and delivering desktop applications, as well as rich Internet applications that can run across a wide variety of devices.","score":"2.6072268841307813","choices":["Boston","America","JavaFX","San Antonio"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257268"},"question":"What requires the presence of a software platform in order for compiled programs to be executed?","answer":"the Java programming language","sentence":"The Java programming language requires the presence of a software platform in order for compiled programs to be executed.","score":"2.606787856043403","choices":["the C broadcasts arabic","the C++ broadcast word","the Java programming language","the Python programs english"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257269"},"question":"What do programs written in Java have?","answer":"a reputation for being slower","sentence":"Programs written in Java have a reputation for being slower and requiring more memory than those written in C + +.","score":"2.6059205457396986","choices":["a image for being slowing","a reputation for being slower","a tarnished for being faster","a credibility for being slow"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425726a"},"question":"What has faded the necessity of having an explicit destructor method in the classes more difficult?","answer":"the presence of a garbage collector","sentence":"Paradoxically, the presence of a garbage collector has faded the necessity of having an explicit destructor method in the classes, thus rendering the management of these other resources more difficult.","score":"2.603181360302202","choices":["the absence of a rubbish collection","the forces of a waste dealer","the presence of a garbage collector","the force of a trash connoisseur"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425726b"},"question":"What is guaranteed to be triggered if there is insufficient free memory on the heap to allocate a new object?","answer":"garbage collection","sentence":"It is guaranteed to be triggered if there is insufficient free memory on the heap to allocate a new object; this can cause a program to stall momentarily.","score":"2.602251744698185","choices":["rubbish museum","trash collected","garbage collection","waste art"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425726c"},"question":"What Sun sued in 1997 as well as a court order enforcing?","answer":"the terms of the license from Sun","sentence":"Sun sued in 1997, and, in 2001, won a settlement of US$20 million, as well as a court order enforcing the terms of the license from Sun.","score":"2.6019167223775583","choices":["the context of the licensing from Sillicon Graphics","the term of the licence from IBM","the terms of the license from Sun","the agreement of the licences from Red Hat Software"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425726d"},"question":"What featured APIs optimized for mobile applications?","answer":"j2ME","sentence":"J2EE included technologies and APIs for enterprise applications typically run in server environments, while J2ME featured APIs optimized for mobile applications.","score":"2.6017526320926048","choices":["PeopleSoft","j2ME","AMD","Red Hat Software"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425726e"},"question":"What offers an implementation compatible with the standard library?","answer":"Java 6 and some Java 7 features","sentence":"It supports Java 6 and some Java 7 features, offering an implementation compatible with the standard library (Apache Harmony).","score":"2.5994768960686603","choices":["Python 8 and some Python 8 featured","C 5 and some C 6 feature","Java 6 and some Java 7 features","C++ 4 and some C++ 9 featuring"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b425726f"},"question":"When did the first public implementation promise Write Once providing on popular platforms?","answer":"no-cost run-times","sentence":"It promised Write Once, Run Anywhere, providing no-cost run-times on popular platforms.","score":"2.595999161585128","choices":["intoxicant run-times","point-to-multipoint run-times","non-coercive run-times","no-cost run-times"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257270"},"question":"What does Oracle follow Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems in?","answer":"in 200910","sentence":"Following Oracle Corporation's acquisition of Sun Microsystems in 200910, Oracle has described itself as the steward of Java technology with a relentless commitment to fostering a community of participation and transparency.","score":"2.5913481435333683","choices":["in 200910","in 200910","in 200910","in 200910"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257271"},"question":"What is controlled by Sun Microsystems in cooperation with others through the Java Community Process program?","answer":"swing","sentence":"It is controlled by Sun Microsystems in cooperation with others through the Java Community Process program.","score":"2.5897932566418196","choices":["swung","pendulum","swing","swinging"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257272"},"question":"What is the Android SDK?","answer":"an alternative software platform","sentence":"The Android SDK is an alternative software platform, used primarily for developing Android applications with its own GUI system.","score":"2.5890973375846396","choices":["an ways hardware support","an alternate microsoft framework","an alternative software platform","an viable computer supports"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257273"},"question":"What does Java mean that compiled Java code can run on?","answer":"on all platforms that support Java without the need for recompilation","sentence":"It is intended to let application developers write once, run anywhere, meaning that compiled Java code can run on all platforms that support Java without the need for recompilation.","score":"2.587021744592826","choices":["on all platforms that support Java without the need for recompilation","on all platform that supported C no the needed for recompiling","on all rigs that supporting C++ any the must for sentimentalizing","on all terminals that backing Python not the should for recompile"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257274"},"question":"What does the Java virtual machine for the overhead of interpreting bytecode into machine instructions translate the Java bytecode into?","answer":"into the platform's machine language","sentence":"Java itself is platform-independent and is adapted to the particular platform it is to run on by a Java virtual machine for it, which translates the Java bytecode into the platform's machine language.","score":"2.5840867624942043","choices":["into the support's guns english","into the framework's gun word","into the supports's automatic arabic","into the platform's machine language"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257275"},"question":"What was the Java 1. 0 compiler re-written in by Arthur van Hoff to comply strictly with the Java 1. 0 language specification?","answer":"in Java","sentence":"The Java 1. 0 compiler was re-written in Java by Arthur van Hoff to comply strictly with the Java 1. 0 language specification.","score":"2.5832437610742454","choices":["in C","in Java","in Python","in C++"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5de4fe284774ead1b4257276"},"question":"Who was Java originally developed by?","answer":"by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems","sentence":"Java was originally developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems (which has since been acquired by Oracle) and released in 1995 as a core component of Sun Microsystems ' Java platform.","score":"2.5814372738114386","choices":["by Richard Mccullam phillippe at moon netscape","by David Hyland callum at sunlight cisco","by John Thomas ryan at microsystems novell","by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems"],"difficulty":"H","correctAttempts":0,"totalOccurrences":0}
